[Music]
Today our company ICICI LBD and its
quarter 2 result is coming
tomorrow i.e. on 14th October, we will
talk about what the numbers and results will be like,
so here you will see that the company is worth Rs
91000 crores on which there
are no debts, according to the industry PE, the
PE of the stock here
we are seeing is 34, it is less
which is quite correct.
And if we talk about ROCE, it is
quite decent here.  End ROE is also seen at 18%.  The
book value is ₹306 and the stock is trading
near the ₹1800 level.  The company
also pays a small dividend.
If we look at the performance of the whole year, we have seen a lot of ups and
downs.  Currently the stock is
seen in a consolidation zone.
Which we have seen between the level of 2100 and 1700.  The
level of 1700 was
also crossed in between.  But again he came inside it and
started trading.  And here you will
see that the movement of the stock is
consolidation.   There are a
lot of ups and downs here.  If we talk about the
results, then its sales in the last quarter were
seen to be quite good.  Along with this, expenses also
reduced considerably here.  Due to which
good profit was made.  Margins increased and net
profit increased.  Now let's look at
how Quarter 2 looks like.  So you
will see that there are very good sales.  At the same time,
expenses are also happening and increasing
but profit is being made.  Margins
are similar but net profit is also increasing.
So there are chances of overall positive results that
we may get to see good positive results of ICICI LB.
So guys, that's all for today's
video.  Like,
share the video, subscribe to the channel.  Thank
you so much for watching this video.